http://www.citizenbike.com/privacy.asp

gallery
TOKYO ($289)
MIAMI ($299)
MILAN ($279)
SEOUL ($419)
GOTHAM7 ($499)
GOTHAM 24-7 ($519)
BARCELONA ($549)
ROME ($439)
FRISCO ($489)
Citizen Bike Inc. (“Citizen Bike”) is committed to
protecting your privacy. This Privacy Statement is designed to inform you about
the manner in which we treat the collection, use, and disclosure of information
that you may provide to us via our website as well as our family of websites.
What information is captured from visitors to the website?
For each visitor to the website, Citizen Bike’s servers automatically
collect information about which pages are visited and for how long, as well as
the IP address, browser type, operating platform of visitors, and other
available information embedded in the visitors visit. This information is
anonymous and is gathered through our servers’ log files. This information is
used for internal review, to tailor information to individual visitors and for
website traffic audits. We also may provide this information (as well as
information from third-party market researchers) about our users on an
aggregated, anonymous basis to our affiliates and strategic partners.
Is personal information requested by the website?
We only solicit personal information from website visitors
on a voluntary basis. Such information may include your name, address,
telephone number, and other order processing information when relevant. Citizen
Bike does not require this information to obtain access to any part of our website.
Citizen Bike has no intention of collecting any personal data from individuals
under 13 years of age.  Upon product
ordering, additional information is collected for order processing purposes.  This information is transmitted to our servers
through SSL encryption in order to protect the transmission of information.
How is the information used?
Personal information collected from you through the website
is used by Citizen Bike to enable us to answer questions and process requests
that are received electronically. We also may use this information to send you
e-mail or other notices about updates to the website or Citizen Bike’s
products. You will always have the option to opt out of any such mailing list.
We do not sell, rent, or lease personal information to third parties.
What happens if I e-mail Citizen Bike?
Citizen Bike may provide email links on the Website to
further facilitate communication between Citizen Bike and you. Information
collected through electronic mail may be shared with our customer service
department, employees or other third parties that perform services on our
behalf. Unless otherwise noted, electronic mail on our site is not a completely
secure and confidential means of communication. Non-encrypted electronic
communications may be accessed and viewed by other Internet users without your
knowledge or permission while in transit to us.
What happens when I leave the website to visit a linked
site?
Parts of the Website include hyperlinks to the sites of
other companies. When you leave our website to visit one of these sites, the
only information transferred to the third party is the fact that you came from our
website (the referrer address). This practice allows the third party to monitor
its own website traffic, but does not provide it with any information about
you. Citizen Bike is not responsible or liable for the independent privacy
policies of third party sites. You should consult the privacy policies at those
sites to determine how your information may be used.
Are cookies used?
Other than a temporary cookies used to maintain the session
state while you visit and shop at the website, Citizen Bike does not currently
place additional cookies on your computer. Citizen Bike may determine at a
later date to place a different type of cookie in the application folder of
your computer’s browser. A cookie itself does not contain any personally
identifying information. Once placed on your computer, a cookie will allow the website
to recognize your computer as a unique visitor to the website.
Is my information secure?
Citizen Bike has taken measures to keep all information from
our online visitors as secure as possible against any unauthorized access or
use. All information is protected by standard security measures which are periodically
reviewed. Unless otherwise noted, electronic mail on our site is not a
completely secure and confidential means of communication. Non-encrypted
electronic communications may be accessed and viewed by other Internet users
without your knowledge or permission while in transit to us.
In addition, we use SSL to encrypt our web pages. SSL is the
leading standard for encrypting and transmitting sensitive data over the web. When
you see "https" rather than "http" in your browsers address
window, you are exchanging encrypted data with our server. This will prevent
outsiders from obtaining any credit card information or personal data as it is
sent to our servers. Secure transactions for this website are done with a private
certificate to ensure secure transmission of your information.
How do I contact Citizen Bike?
We can be reached via our contact us page.
Notice regarding changes to Privacy Statement.
Citizen Bike may change the foregoing Privacy Statement from
time to time without notice by posting the changed Privacy Statement on the website.
This Privacy Statement is not intended to and does not create any contractual
or other legal right in or on behalf of any party.
folding bike shop
portable & folding bikes
Folding Bicycles by Citizen Bike for commuting, travel and just around town – riding bikes has never been so much fun.
folding bike bags
Carrying bags for your folding Citizen bike for travel, storage and convenience.
folding bike accessories
Gear up! Everything you need to accessorize you and your Citizen folding bike – helmets, racks, fenders, seats & more.
citizen goodies
Yes, proud Citizens. You can get your very own Citizen socks here.
contact us
Need help? Get in touch.
1-800-682-9579
Representatives are available
Monday - Friday, 10am - 4pm EST
Have a question? Send us a note.
contact us
Citizen Bike Inc.
1190 Stirling Rd.
Dania Beach, FL 33004
videos & gallery
See our folding bikes in action.choosing your bike
Citizen Bike offers a variety of folding and portable bicycles to suit all types of uses and budgets.
If you're looking for budget conscious folder to a lightweight commuter, Citizen Bike has a bike for your lifestyle. Learn more about choosing the most appropriate model for you.
folding bike shop
portable & folding bikes
Folding Bicycles by Citizen Bike for commuting, travel and just around town – riding bikes has never been so much fun.
folding bike bags
Carrying bags for your folding Citizen bike for travel, storage and convenience.
folding bike accessories
Gear up! Everything you need to accessorize you and your Citizen folding bike – helmets, racks, fenders, seats & more.
citizen goodies
Yes, proud Citizens. You can get your very own Citizen socks here.
contact us
Need help? Get in touch.
1-800-682-9579
Representatives are available
Monday - Friday, 10am - 4pm EST
Have a question? Send us a note.
contact us
Citizen Bike Inc.
1190 Stirling Rd.
Dania Beach, FL 33004
videos & gallery
See our folding bikes in action.choosing your bike
Citizen Bike offers a variety of folding and portable bicycles to suit all types of uses and budgets.
If you're looking for budget conscious folder to a lightweight commuter, Citizen Bike has a bike for your lifestyle. Learn more about choosing the most appropriate model for you.
BARCELONA
GOTHAM7
GOTHAM 24-7
SEOUL
MILAN
MIAMI
TOKYO
ROME
Need help?
Contact us.
(800) 682-9579
Need help? Get in touch.
1-800-682-9579
Representatives are available
Monday - Friday, 10am - 4pm EST
